<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Briefly Berners-Lee and Gosling</string>

    <string name="author1_name">Tim Berners-Lee</string>
    <string name="author1_photo_desc">Photo of Tim Berners-Lee</string>
    <string name="author1_attribution">http://www.flickr.com/photos/4nitsirk</string>
    <string name="author1_desc">
    <![CDATA[
        Sir Timothy John \"Tim\" Berners-Lee, OM, KBE, FRS, FREng, FRSA, DFBCS (born 8 June 1955),
        also known as \"TimBL\", is a British computer scientist, best known as the inventor of the
        World Wide Web. He made a proposal for an information management system in March 1989, and
        he implemented the first successful communication between a Hypertext Transfer Protocol (HTTP)
        client and server via the Internet sometime around mid November.\n
        Berners-Lee is the director of the World Wide Web Consortium (W3C), which oversees the Web\'s
        continued development. He is also the founder of the World Wide Web Foundation, and is a senior
        researcher and holder of the Founders Chair at the MIT Computer Science and Artificial Intelligence
        Laboratory (CSAIL). He is a director of the Web Science Research Initiative (WSRI), and a member
        of the advisory board of the MIT Center for Collective Intelligence.
    ]]>
    </string>

    <string name="author2_name">James Gosling</string>
    <string name="author2_photo_desc">Photo of James Gosling</string>
    <string name="author2_attribution">http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/User:Peter_Campbell</string>
    <string name="author2_desc">
    <![CDATA[
        James Arthur Gosling, OC (born May 19, 1955) is a Canadian computer scientist, best known as the
        father of the Java programming language.\n
        Gosling is generally credited with having invented the Java programming language in 1994. He
        created the original design of Java and implemented the language\'s original compiler and virtual
        machine.\n
        Gosling traces the origins of the approach to his early 19s graduate-student days, when he created
        a pseudo-code (p-code) virtual machine for the lab\'s DEC VAX computer, so that his professor could
        run programs written in UCSD Pascal. Pascal compiled into p-code to foster precisely this kind of
        portability. In the work leading to Java at Sun, he saw that architecture-neutral execution for
        widely distributed programs could be achieved by implementing a similar philosophy: always program
        for the same virtual machine.
    ]]>
    </string>
</resources>
